dediseedbox.com 2010-11-26

# Dedi Seedbox - Knowledgebase - Privacy Policy

[Portal Home](http://dediseedbox.com/clients/index.php) > [Knowledgebase](http://dediseedbox.com/clients/knowledgebase.php) > [General](http://dediseedbox.com/clients/knowledgebase.php?action=displaycat&catid=9) > [Privacy Policy](http://dediseedbox.com/clients/knowledgebase.php?action=displayarticle&id=30)

## Privacy Policy

Dedi Seedbox values your privacy.  Please read the following information about how we handle your information.

Personal Information:  
Your personal information is never shared to any other parties or law enforcements unless fradulent credit card or paypal charges have occurred.

Website:  
Google analytics collects your IP address, browser type and operating system on each visit to every page on this site on our behalf.  This information is used ONLY for internal statistic tracking purposes and is never shared with other entities outside dedi seedbox.  

E-Mail:  
Dedi seedbox does not send bulk e-mail messages, or 'Spam'.  We only communicate with our current clients.  
We will, on occassion, send all of our clients a group e-mail when special offers, price changes, software updates or important issues arise.  If you believe you have received bulk e-mail from us, or have received a suspicious e-mail that appears to be fraudulent, please contact us so that we can investigate the matter.  
All e-mail messages received from our clients are kept completely confidential and are never shared with parties outside of dedi seedbox without your express permission.  
We do not have an automated mail-list system because we send all of our e-mails manually.  

|   
---|---  
  
Also Read
